mobilerdx.com 2017-09-20

# Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use

What follows is the Privacy Statement and Terms of Use for all https://www.mobilerdx.com websites including all the websites run under the https://www.mobilerdx.com domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

Email Address: prateet000@gmail.com

We respects our readers & visitors privacy. We do collects our visitors personal information like log files including your IP addresses, browser,Operating Systems, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), location , referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.We are collecting such information not for selling or sharing purpose but for improving the information and resource provided by us. such information like This Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.

**Ownership of Information:**  
https://www.mobilerdx.com is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Cookie and Advertisement policy:**

To maintain our website free of charge we shows third party advertisements on our website from Google Adsense.Google as a third part vendor use cookie to show advertisement on our website so it may store cookies in your computer. You may opt-out from Google’s Dart cookie from <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>

**Comments/Message Boards:**  
Websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Links:**  
https://www.mobilerdx.com websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by https://www.mobilerdx.com

**Disclaimer:**  
We are not affiliated with any cell phone companies that are mentioned through out all our website. Logos, Trademarks and Names of Mobile phone manufacturers like [Nokia](https://www.mobilerdx.com/category/nokia), [Samsung](https://www.mobilerdx.com/category/samsung), Sony Ericsson, Samsung, Lg and [Motorola](https://www.mobilerdx.com/category/motorola) are the property of their respective owners. We Just provide Mobile Phones Repairing Imaged for study and information purposes.

**We are not responsible for any damage or loss:**  
Since each and every post has solutions which at least one member of our team has checked before we post it on our website. But still we don’t take any responsibility if something is damaged or lost. Do anything at your own risk.
